flash-slide-show.com 2009-05-03

# Wondershare Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Wondershare recognizes that our customers value their right to privacy and want to be assured that any personal information that they provide to us will be used in accordance with their wishes. Wondershare is committed to ensuring that you are fully informed as to how your personal information will be used and that it will be kept secure.

**What information do we collect?**

Wondershare may collect personal information from you relating both to your identity and personal preferences as well as our products. Wondershare will endeavor only to collect such information as is necessary for the stated purpose for which we are collecting the information. For example if you purchase a Wondershare product, we will require your name and address so that we can send the product to you and your credit card details to obtain payment. Wherever possible Wondershare will provide you with clear information as to the type of information, we wish to collect and how we want to use it. You will be given a clear option to agree or not agree to such information being collected. If we require further information, we will clearly set out the information we wish to collect and the purposes for which we are collecting it.

**Purposes for which we Use Information**

Our objective is to inform you before or at the time of collection as to the information we are collecting and the purposes for which we wish to use such information. We will seek your clear consent to your information being used for the stated purposes and will only collect such information as is reasonably necessary to achieve those purposes. Wondershare will clearly inform you as to information that it requires to proceed with the stated purpose and information that is merely optional. If you choose not to provide required information Wondershare may not be able to comply with your request or provide certain services. 

**Sharing of Information with Third Parties**

We may share the information that you have provided to us with subsidiaries and affiliated companies of Wondershare Corporation. Such affiliated companies will also comply with the terms of this policy.

In an effort to offer our customers the maximum benefit of Wondershare's strategic and co-branding partnerships, we also undertake co-marketing agreements with third parties who offer similar products or services or who may collect your personal information, identifiable or non-identifiable, in order to provide certain online services to you. Wondershare may share profile information with its co-branding partners in order to better personalize the content, banners and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites. Advertising partners or other online services partners of Wondershare may use their own cookies.  
As a registered Wondershare customer, you will have the option of receiving news and special offers from third parties. You will have the option of declining such communications when you provide us with you information or at any other time. 

**How do 3rd party credit card processors protect customer information?**

Wondershare software uses secure server hosted by SWREG and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition. 

**SWREG**

Swreg is an advanced secure online payment service for software registration that has been in operation since 1987. Wondershare Software uses SWREG to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase. 

**Links**

We may offer links from our website to other websites which may be hosted by our co-branding partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and Wondershare makes no representation as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit.

**About Cookies**

We may make use of "cookies" on our website. A cookie is a small text file that can be placed and stored on your computer's hard disc when you visit a website for record keeping purposes. A cookie itself is not designed or intended to read any information from a user's computer (other than the contents of the cookie); rather, it is an identifier used by the Web site that originally placed it on your hard drive. The actual contents of the cookie information can be retrieved by the same server to identify the computer and subsequently to customize, monitor, or regulate the use of a site based on information stored on the host server. Therefore, cookies only identify the user's computer to the Web site which may correlate other information, including personally identifying information, with the cookie.

We use cookies to allow us to automate access and the data entry functions of our website such as to correlate online ordering information for purchases you may make while at the website (if any), tailor our website to your preferences or interests, or customize promotions or marketing. In addition, cookies allow us to track use of our website to determine those areas which are useful or popular and those that are not thereby enabling us to improve and update our website effectively.

Most web browsers can either alert you to the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. If you are not sure how to do this or whether you have this option you should consult the documentation that accompanied your web browser. You should be aware that if you elect not to accept cookies, some parts of the website may not function properly or permit access.
